Sections

1. [1\. Privacy policy.](#privacy-policy-)
2. [2\. GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (GDPR)](#general-data-protection-regulation--gdpr-)
3. [3\. PRIVACY POLICIES](#privacy-policies)
4. [4\. THIRD-PARTY PRIVACY POLICIES](#third-party-privacy-policies)
5. [5\. CHILDREN'S INFORMATION](#children-s-information)
6. [6\. CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY](#changes-to-this-privacy-policy)
7. [7\. Online Privacy Policy Only](#online-privacy-policy-only)

### Privacy policy.

At Samir Zarrouk Photography, accessible from https://samirzarrouk.com, one of our main priorities is the privacy of our visitors. This Privacy Policy document contains types of information that is collected and recorded by Samir Zarrouk Photography and how we use it.

If you have additional questions or require more information about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us: By visiting this page on our website: [https://samirzarrouk.com/](https://samirzarrouk.com/contact)[con](https://samirzarrouk.com/contact)[tact](https://samirzarrouk.com/contact)

#### GENERAL DATA PROTECTION REGULATION (GDPR)

We are a Data Controller of your information. If you'd like to learn more about GDPR and your rights under GDPR.

Samir Zarrouk Photography's legal basis for collecting and using the personal information described in this Privacy Policy depends on the Personal Information we collect and the specific context in which we collect the information:

* Samir Zarrouk Photography needs to perform a contract with you
    
* You have given Samir Zarrouk Photography permission to do so
    
* Processing your personal information is in Samir Zarrouk Photography's legitimate interests
    
* Samir Zarrouk Photography needs to comply with the law

Samir Zarrouk Photography will retain your personal information only for as long as is necessary for the purposes set out in this Privacy Policy. We will retain and use your information to the extent necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our policies.

If you are a resident of the European Economic Area (EEA), you have certain data protection rights. If you wish to be informed what Personal Information we hold about you and if you want it to be removed from our systems, please contact us.

In certain circumstances, you have the following data protection rights:

* The right to access, update or delete the information we have on you.
    
* The right of rectification.
    
* The right to object.
    
* The right of restriction.
    
* The right to data portability
    
* The right to withdraw consent

**Log Files**

Samir Zarrouk Photography follows a standard procedure of using log files. These files log visitors when they visit websites. All hosting companies do this and are a part of hosting services' analytics. The information collected by log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date and time stamp, referring/exit pages, and possibly the number of clicks. These are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. The purpose of the information is for analyzing trends, administering the site, tracking users' movement on the website, and gathering demographic information.

**Cookies and Web Beacons**

Like any other website, Samir Zarrouk Photography uses 'cookies. These cookies are used to store information including visitors' preferences, and the pages on the website that the visitor accessed or visited. The information is used to optimize the users' experience by customizing our web page content based on visitors browser type and/or other information.

You can learn how to manage cookies on your web browser by following the [Browser Cookies Guide](https://privacypolicies.com/blog/browser-cookies-guide/).

#### PRIVACY POLICIES

You may consult this list to find the Privacy Policy for each of the advertising partners of Samir Zarrouk Photography.

Third-party ad servers or ad networks uses technologies like cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons that are used in their respective advertisements and links that appear on Samir Zarrouk Photography, which are sent directly to users' browser. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. These technologies are used to measure the effectiveness of their advertising campaigns and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see on websites that you visit.

Note that Samir Zarrouk Photography has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

#### THIRD-PARTY PRIVACY POLICIES

Samir Zarrouk Photography's Privacy Policy does not apply to other advertisers or websites. Thus, we are advising you to consult the respective Privacy Policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information. It may include their practices and instructions about how to opt-out of certain options. You may find a complete list of these Privacy Policies and their links here: Privacy Policy Links.

You can choose to disable cookies through your individual browser options. To know more detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers, it can be found on the browsers' respective websites. What Are Cookies?

#### CHILDREN'S INFORMATION

Another part of our priority is adding protection for children while using the internet. We encourage parents and guardians to observe, participate in, and/or monitor and guide their online activity.

Samir Zarrouk Photography does not knowingly collect any Personal Identifiable Information from children under the age of 13. If you think that your child provided this kind of information on our website, we strongly encourage you to contact us immediately and we will do our best efforts to promptly remove such information from our records.

#### CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY

The Owner reserves the right to make changes to this privacy policy at any time by giving notice to its Users on this page and possibly within this Application and/or - as far as technically and legally feasible - sending a notice to Users via any contact information available to the Owner. It is strongly recommended to check this page often, referring to the date of the last modification listed at the bottom. 

##### Online Privacy Policy Only

Our Privacy Policy created at GDPRPrivacyPolicy.net) applies only to our online activities and is valid for visitors to our website with regard to the information that they shared and/or collect in Samir Zarrouk Photography. This policy is not applicable to any information collected offline or via channels other than this website.

**Consent**

By using our website, you hereby consent to our Privacy Policy and agree to its terms.
